Ningninghou: Here's the deal.
Ningninghou: Let's scout the area first.
Ningninghou: So, um...
Ningninghou: Nan, you take this area, okay?
Nan Nandu: Okay.
Ningninghou: This area.
Jin Jinliang: Then I'll take that area.
Ningninghou: Okay, you take that area.
Ningninghou: What about you?
Ke Ke'ai: I'll search around the dining table.
Ningninghou: The dining table.
He Heda: Then I'll take this area.
He Heda: I'll take this area.
Ningninghou: This area.
Nan Nandu: There's one up there too.
Nan Nandu: Remember to check it.
He Heda: Okay.
Countdown starts.
Ningninghou: Check that one too.
Dingdingdang: There's something under this table.
Li Liwo: There's a sound.
Li Liwo: Intruder!
Li Liwo: Someone's here.
Nan Nandu: Don't touch me!
30 seconds deducted.
He Heda: Just you wait!
Li Liwo: What?
Li Liwo: Who's here?
Li Liwo: What's that sound?
30 seconds deducted.
Li Liwo: What? What's this?
Li Liwo: What's this?
Li Liwo: It's not human.
Li Liwo: What else?
Li Liwo: What else is there?
Li Liwo: Who's this?
30 seconds deducted.
Ningninghou: Wait, my earring fell off.
Ningninghou: My earring fell off.
Li Liwo: This room is full of people!
30 seconds deducted.
Dingdingdang: We definitely failed this time.
Dingdingdang: Quick, be brave and look!
Jin Jinliang: Is there a key?
Countdown ended.
Challenge failed.
Please remain where you are.
Countdown will restart in three minutes.
He Heda: Let's rest for a minute.
Ningninghou: Just now, you guys...
Ningninghou: Why did you come over here?
Ningninghou: Are you done searching over there?